ZARIFAHANIS BT BAKAR

Address: No. 26, Lorong Shahbandar 33, Bertam Perdana 3, 13200 Kepala Batas, Pulau Pinang.

Phone: 012-9272345 | Email: hanis4sit@gmail.com



CAREER OBJECTIVE

Dedicated and motivated graduate equipped with experience in performing scientific research, producing scientific report, and working in teams. Possessing a passion in contributing my skills and experience to works as a hardworking employee in a professional organisation.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science with Honours Biotechnology 2013 - 2016

• University of Nottingham Malaysia Campus

• Second Class Upper

• Results: 67%

Foundation of Science

2012 - 2013

University of Nottingham Malaysia Campus

Second Class Upper

• Results : 65%

Sijil Pelajaran Malaysia

2010-2011

Mara Junior Science College KubangPasu

Results: 4A+, 3A, 2A-, 1B+

 First Class Honours in overall academic achievement for 2010 and 2011.

3rd Year Final Year Project (Research)- Role of biocontrol agent, *Trichodermaasperellum* on the infection Of *GanodermaBoninense LS*. in young Oil palm *In Vitro*.

Analysing the effectiveness of fungus *T.asperellum* to reduce Basal Stem Root (BSR) infection on Oil
Palm cause by fungus *G. boninense* at physical and molecular level by performing experiments such
as Polymerase Chain Reaction (PCR), Quantitative PCR (qPCR), DNA sequencing and Microscopic
analysis.

WORKING EXPERIENCE

School of Bioscience, University of Nottingham Malaysia Campus. [8 June 2015 – 28 August 2015]

Summer Internship Programme 2015 with UNMC

Working professionally as Research assistant with project entitle "Molecular Interaction of *GanodermaBoninense*Pathogenesis In Oil Palm". Learned advance research skill include

- 1. Conducting enzyme assay experiments
- 2. Performing Polymerase Chain Reaction (PCR) and Quantitative PCR (qPCR)
- 3. Sub-culture and maintaining Ganoderma and Trichoderma fungus culture
- 4. Performing Gel electrophoresis and DNA recovery for sequencing
- 5. Performing DNA, RNA extraction and cDNA synthesis

CURRICULUM

Clubs	Year	Achievements	
Bioscience Students in Nottingham	2012-2016	Developing team work and presentation skill by participate in organising Bioscience Awareness	
		Weeks.	
Community Service	September	Planning and conducting mural painting at	
	2015	S.J.K.T LadangSemenyih	
Volunteering	2012-2016	Feed the Homeless with NGO	
		Nottingham Charity Cycling 2014	
		 Organising Earth hour event with 	
		Nottingham Nature Club	
Seminar	June 2014	Esco Safety Awareness on Laminar Flow, Biological	
		Safety Cabinet &Fume Hood Technology	
Class Representative	2010-2011	Appointed as class representative for two years	
Kadet Polis Wanita	2008-2011	First Place in PertandinganKawad Kaki peringkat	
		Daerah Baling for 2008 and 2009	

SKILLS

Personal skills

- Competent, multi-task and result oriented
- Effective management, highly organized and efficient
- Ability to work independently or as part of a team
- Use clear, concise communication skills in conjunction with organizational skills to perform daily duties.

Computer skills

- Microsoft Words, Excell, Powerpoints .
- Statistic Software such as SPSS and Genstat and Graphpad

Language

	Written	Spoken
Bahasa Malaysia	5/5	5/5
English	3/5	3/5

REFERENCES:

Ms Christina VimalaSupramaniam

Assistant Professor School of Bioscience University of Nottingham Malaysia Campus christina.supramaniam@nottingham.edu.my **Dr Winnie Yap**

Lecturer and Module Convenor School of Bioscience University of Nottingham Malaysia Campus. Winnie.Yap@nottingham.edu.my